they and
[music]
we will continue to talk almost cheats and the
next section here it says if you
his death the first step for bodhicitta is
when you think of all people equally equally
tackle and
realize and admit that all people
were your mother
remember what they did for you when they
were your mothers and and you want to pay
for what they do for you where they
were mothers before you
these steps are the basis
[music]
to want to work for others this is the
basis and so what is the basis
think of everyone equally recognize that
everyone was your mother remember what they
did for you when they were your mothers
and
you and then you naturally you
want to repay them not these 4 in
fact three and a half are the
basis the desire to want to work for
other people and then here it says
another way to
want these people to be happy
the desire to take away all their problems and protsa
flag sam nanda I will take care of everything it doesn't
matter that no one will help me
no it doesn't even matter that people will want to
stop me it doesn't matter
I
will still do it for  no, and if people
actively try to
stop you, it doesn't matter, I'll do
it anyway, it's all ours, not me, I'll
do it, I'll take care of everything,
these are the ideas,
I want them to be happy, I want to
take away all their problems,
I'm the one who will take care,
and even if someone doesn't help
me, it doesn't matter even if everyone is against
me, I'll still continue to help them,
not this is called a true desire to
work for others,
so part 1 of these seven was called
laying the foundation to work for
others, and
now we're moving on to parts to work for
the sake of a fight, and
so here's the first picture, I'll work
for here, he has
you, like Daniel on a good
day, he has this builder's cap, I'll do it,
don't worry, I have mine, they're
protecting my cap, I'll take care,
no one will help you, it doesn't matter, I don't care,
I'll fight against you, I won't
interfere with you, it doesn't matter, it's all on me, I did it, I'll
take care of everything,
and
then we move on to the author comes to a
very important part of this book on
banks, honor,
as soon as you decide, you kind of decide
what you  will work for the sake of others, we
can say,
repeat yourself, and according to it, what is Danchev's
mandate, Jobs
[music], we
will define Bucky, read
the most famous definition of Botice, you in
history, who wrote it,
that wrote both the most
Alan Koru, and these are
translators for 10, Maitreya will work
correctly, this is from a book that translates a
type called
precious serialization, an inscription
written 1700 years ago, and
in this book he mentions the definition of
depriving you of them, since then, it was
famous
until sleep during debates, the monastery, you
say, what is the definition of
bodhichitta, and you call this
definition, and this is complete, April,
who gave this definition, the future of the year,
white ray, and
who said this,
this is another question, and this was my debate,
which I am about the department before becoming
beshe, here it is, the translation of these two lines, the
same definition of
tire chorba, the good of all living beings,
index n, miracle, I want to become, I will be, this is
here, this focuses on two
relationships, he rests, firstly,
on other people, and we succeeded,
this is a double focus, this is a relationship
where from a double focus, I will call, I will take care
and everyone who is in all of all
universes, I want to become Gudovich, don't
focus on everyone who has problems
in this world, and I want to become the one who can
help them. This is the definition of a
batnik, and it's like, come on, it contains a
double focus, a
direction in this definition, and I
thought it would be very interesting if we
fill in the sanctions.
Originally, it was written in
Sanskrit. The Sanskrit language would
not be this line. It's very, very, very
famous.
They say that if you want to
become an enlightened being in your heart,
remember a little Sanskrit,
and remember a few Sanskrit words. And
so, I've prepared for you. I
now have a new person who
translates Sanskrit.
Then
[music]
when you see, go to such a long
stick, a
dash above the letter, and that means a
long poet will repeat, learn someone's top, we'll pull it up,
and
[music] there are
no long ones here, but short ones.
[music]
PMS.   With
.  n from below
you speak like the French as if you were
stuck here and it's wild and then
let's repeat it together slowly
[music]
and
to I
[music]
okay
try to remember this phrase
if
if you are too lazy
to pronounce a long line you
can use this short one
che that means
like someone's beekeepers
fall I mean
when someone meets with fell she she she will
turn into something
serving taub until
fall turns into cheat memory
this means
this means I will raise
increase or raise
exalt
this is to achieve under hichet
this is a variation of this word someone's fields a couple of
places a couple means other people
what is it called
parameters when you cross to the other
side what does it mean time metaphor in on
Thursdays people
what does it mean attack always everyone arches goal
arata is the goal and other people parade-alle
[music]
city this means the goal and other people what
other people want that I don't see
and I at the end of the word means for the sake of not for the
good in order to achieve this and
such at the end of the couple that means
for the good of the
goal of the desires of others, this
means for the sake of
prefixes in Sanskrit, they at the end became
the apparatus
samyak, meaning I remember completely one hundred
percent myself, 100% process completely
[ __ ] dikom means once enlightened himself,
means ideal body, means
enlightenment body, and
amato, repeat amata
[music]
this is the desire to achieve the
desire to achieve mother, meaning this, this
mentally comes from this word, and at the
beginning it is
long, at the
beginning the word
means
very-very-very, therefore we say, a, it is
necessary, very happy, and if she does, it means you
think if you are a person, therefore, at
the beginning it means very, therefore
long, and who really wants a
bar, hold these thoughts,
thoughts about ideal enlightenment for
the good of all living beings,
beings, and this is
the definition reading pazu patches cheats and it
seems to me you need to learn this, remember
in Russian it means to read I think I think
I think whether I read
this to count this means to count in cheats for
rus in Russian the Sanskrit roots are
not much more obvious
pat to
fall, for example,
to fall,
some guy wrote a book
I
and
also  does
this mean forbid does it mean to
fall or does it mean a stupa of
fall does it mean to rise up meat
decline
accounts of fall this is to raise this desire to
raise or there this thought so that this
thought appeared in you rose
yours not
dates what does cedar mean
what does sid means
achieved visited goal cedar it means
achieved goal and I mean for the benefit of all
others price means full himself bots
means enlightened she is there I want
my mind my consciousness are turned that's how
cool yes try it remember this is a
cool definition the
next picture those with
them
here and there is no emphasis on the
barrels cheat which you want to wear will be
I want to achieve this I want to achieve this
to help everyone here
he is looking forward I would
like to achieve this and then I
can really help people
cool yes and
so according to Blanca Rinpoche at this point in the
book
gives the most famous
construction that was ever written
about
botice tu and who
wrote these lines Maitreya and who
wrote down his words ari and he himself wrote down the
words iframe and
what famous school started areas
on when he only
What famous book did his half-
brother start? Your bank, he started resentment. ru.
What do these two principles have in common?
Ok, I want a different answer.
100 dollars.
Ask
about
take money, take it, or, well,
it's not her problem to give out money. You
even
hope that everyone will ask for money
only for the money that you can't earn. Cool,
these two half-brothers are
not from the heart. They are both from a
middle-school,
but since the students around them were
stupid and his name is stupid, and dust is
stupid,
they simplified these teachings. He's not a master of
your mind.
He seems to be
telling both dorns, a
master, and posture. He tells
schools only. And recently, we looked at the
teaching about seeds and schools only.
[music]
zinc. He highly appreciates
the description of the family, the
school presentation. He only talks about seeds.
He says it's very useful for tantra. You
can't imagine this.
It must be very cool.
[music]
These are complex questions.
I should have given you more
money for
me or lines.
And now he says, here, let's talk.
What does complete mean? Here, to boast about a
completed place.  Someone asks you to
define complete botice, some yes,
only says if you want to talk about
plugs, what's there that are completely
finished, complete,
not enough,
you kind of want to achieve, I
will be you, because others need it,
according to the race, he says
this is a technical definition, but this is not
enough,
just your desire to achieve vigor,
because others
need it, something is needed here, and it is added,
something else, and what does it add?
You must
come to lysozyme, to the realization that you have
no choice but to become
yourself, I will be, that's how it is
in the definition,
this is to achieve wisdom so that you can
help others, the floor says someone
must add, you have no other choice,
you must do this,
you must do this, I need to do this,
I must do this, he
clouds, he
objects, Maitreya, the
bank of
May, Maitreya, says I want to become, I will,
what will help, about the frame, says this is all, what is it to
create,
what else do you need? I don't have such a
choice, I need to do this, it's not
that I want to do this,
I object, your mother, and I
object, I
wish, this is necessary, he says to us, I have no
other choice, no need to become, it will be
very interesting, according to the bank, he kind of
objects to Maitreya
[music] A
cage is what kind of desire is this, this is
an obligation, I have no other choice and the
bastard wants [ __ ] licked,
I have no choice, no, I need to do this on the
stoves, this is and Dima in the secret language
that means I have no other
choice.
When you say amato in Sanskrit,
the desire to achieve, if you mean I have
another choice, then I agree, and
if you didn't think that I had no other way
out, then
your definition is weak, and
now what will happen to this person
someday, the motor,
how did the body begin to look? I have
no choice, I need to do this
in American English, and you need to
do this. I have no other choice, I
must do this. When you see this, this
mudra,
I have no choice.
When you kill this picture, remember something. It
means that I have grown up differently.
This doesn't know that I can't pay
you today. Become well, okay,
and
then according to the bank, Rinpoche says,
this is not this, not just a desire to
achieve. I will explain myself
not in terms of the three steps we have
already gone through. Jumpa, this is my train. I want
everyone to be happy. Second, Neji. I do
n't want anyone to have problems. 3rd
grade.
I take the heat on myself. I have done everything. I don't care
even if someone doesn't
help me. It doesn't matter if others
fight me. It doesn't matter. This
requires certain spiritual
maturity. You need to understand. You need to
spiritually mature to know I
understand I'm ready to pay your bills
next month I
know you're unhappy it doesn't matter I'll still
make you happy without any what's it
called
you're not without offense people people offend you and
you continue to help help help
and then they words offend you and you still
continue to help so
they criticize you you still don't care here I'll
cook you dinner this is how
you respond to criticism and
when you have bodhichitta with the right
taste for it to be you need these
previous steps
these three I want you to have everything I don't
want you to have problems and I'll
take care of it you don't need to
worry about anything because I take everything upon
myself these
steps they are necessary for you to have the
right connect us conducted with taste
you should have these three thoughts before
this I want you to have everything I don't
want you to have problems and I'll take
care of it and then you can have the
right one in the chat window from these three
thoughts you will have this right
cleaner
this is how it speaks about this here
when you read English on
I  I want to show you another picture,
Timka, are you ready? It
took me some time
until I found this, friends.
I tried to find this picture of a
man with handcuffs. There were a
lot of pictures that would be
unacceptable to show you,
but the meaning of this picture is that you have
no choice.
At this moment, in your mental
state, even if you didn't want to
help, you can't cope with
yourself. You are handcuffed. You are
handcuffed by your own love.
You cannot break free from this
obligation even if you wanted to.
You were handcuffed because
you took three steps. You want
everyone to have everything. You want them not to
suffer. You are ready to do this. And the
results of this are the same. You are on the handbrake, and you
have this vision of yourself. This will
move you toward what
you want.
And you don't control it in a good
way. You can't refuse it
even if you think about it. You can't do it anymore.
Your previous steps in studying patches, cheats,
how it pushes you to move forward, and
this is no longer under your control.
This word, we already had 100 dollars before. A
lot of time has passed since then.
For the sake of-for the sake of no I'm not sure is 100
dollar equal to
be careful of how a day people
earn a lot of money they are funny
time
yes this means that a
dollar movies but you have to collect yourself
take your money a new system
I understand that it will be very noble
works for the benefit of all living beings it will be very noble
this understanding they
want to take away her pain I also I know it will be
very noble to
take responsibility yourself I
understand this it's very noble but in
general you need
this is absolutely possible and the
answer
then says to the children to teach you is not a thing -
you can achieve this the
time has not come dear time has come
you think the best time will be then no then still
divide the time when now I
can achieve this when you have to you do it
today because who knows what
will happen tomorrow it is
unknown whether you will be
tomorrow
maybe you don't know in what field you
will be tomorrow maybe they are with the one who puts forward
these lubricants and
so I don't know if I can achieve this and
then when the bill pick up you don't have you are
still a person then you are still breathing then you must do it
today without asking can do it
you must do it and do it
now who knows where we will alternate
4 purely
that guy can press this button
that will launch the atomic  an atomic bomb,
we all might be on vacation tomorrow,
we don't know, I ask, it's easier,
you can do it and you must
do it now,
there's no better time than now, you've
never had a better chance than now, there's never been a
better time when you need to
do it, when you decide to do it than
now
because you have the
right combination of mind and body,
Lukyanchuk, packs for 100 dollars, what does
that mean, up to
100 dollars, Mr. Walls,
now he's moving in this,
what is he saying here? You have a
body, you have about her, you have
what, you have a channel and you have a
body, you have a mind that is connected
with the help of panov, you are on the
brink of becoming a will, you have a body in
which there are
channels, you have a chakra, you are halfway there
already, you are just doing this stupid thing, the sky
every morning and
then it comes forward and upward at you, you
have a body that was
produced in order to become
the work of an enlightened person, instead of you,
you have these things, these things, these chakras, these
nodes, then you were created to become
enlightened in a factory, you were already
created like this, my factory was already created for
this and  was created with these channels with
this central channel you were created
to become enlightened so
you don't know if not in a dog's body
such good karma yes and not wagging
the tail but
you have an ideal configuration from the point of
view of right from the point of view of tantra you
can do yoga there already do tantra
you were built created for this you
have everything you need
let's do it it's very beautiful
how he jumps over the
crane and about pro no it's cool you were
created initially you were to become
enlightened
what do you want to get out of this bbm
in and piri-piri sowing gets up
you can do it later
you bmw and you can die I have a
friend who doesn't have a bmw
I'm kidding don't take it to heart
everyone who does good practice they
will be successful and
it's not the fault of the
teacher
listen
since you have a body you have you
can achieve enlightenment so
use these you have from the district says about
you have you have
darma will be you have these
student and how do you
have the teaching of
Buddha what about you  You're crazy, you darns, you
'll live to teach others
not only the teachings of
Buddha, you have a picture,
so
you have Makhaya, she can mine,
you're not stuck in school, both Dorn, and
here you have two masters, they translate
the classics of these masters, you're not stuck in
Mahayana, firstly,
we are not the one who doesn't know the teachings, and
secondly, you know the teachings of Buddha, and
having met, you know, Makhaya, we have
100 dollars, what will he say next, that
you have
100 dollars and should take this
money yourself, the new system is good, yes, this is
exactly it, so he goes further,
he also describes the words tan tan Troyana
or diamond Putin says
to repeat
Lotsa
Sochi Platza, we don't
repeat,
tell me the goal,
wife appraiser,
he describes tantra, she's like Sochi Flank,
you have a system
that will help you achieve this in
one life,
he doesn't say tantra, she says in
one life, you are sitting here among a group of
people
so that in that place where the whole
system that will help you achieve this, I will
fill in life, this is in the diamond  Garnier,
here you don't
need to talk about can I
meet the water of anger, they built
this place for you to practice, in J money, this
place can be gram was built for
you to practice,
I am Gene and many people who have worked for many, many
years to prepare
this place for you, I was with Dividends, he
brought students from South Africa, they
speak very strangely, they are
cool,
I am
[music]
you have a place that was built so that
this could be done, so don't
tell me that, where are you going, are you going to go
to Cincinnati, there is
nothing there, you and here, okay,
bunch, no need to say, I will do
it somewhere, somewhere, there is
no better place in the whole universe than
this, seriously, it was built for
these purposes, this place was chosen, the place
was chosen for this, so let's,
you need to do it, okay,
let's look at some pictures,
very slowly, Mr. T, and the first one is
Daniel with his casco hat,
what does that mean,
yes, I am ready to do this work, I am ready to
work for the sake of others, everything, I am ready to k k k k
k and and  7 steps this applies
to the last one whom on average 3 of you you us
science jump they are poor as I think 4
also mentioned these only three and these three and the
base that is needed for this is equal to I know
that not yours were materials to think about
being kind and want to repay them for
it well and
now
what other picture do we have next this is
what definition definition of Maitri
to distinguish with the definition of Hichet and it is also
called
this means that this thought arose this is a
synonym to distinguish cheats it that
Potapovich is a synonym and here is Chita Chita
under
[music]
so I will finish reading
then this definition of Maitri you
need to learn this in Sanskrit and it is not
difficult to
sow good seeds in your consciousness
for enlightenment so you learn this
cool these things memorized
I such things from I had a small and
small
diary yes I wrote down did not memorize the
words
I learned orton and
then walked home read this on the way back
once I forgot this more than
once I memorized this I memorized this more than
once I even forgot my shoes at the
teacher's house
I'll visit the sitar game and I was walking home
and halfway there I realized I was barefoot
and it was hugging and there were roads like that I
returned we are like this now definitely
exist this is still like the head don't
follow the picture this what does it mean I have no
choice I have to do this it's not
enough to say
I want enlightenment for the benefit of all living
beings Maitreya was
wrong or gave an incomplete definition in
fact there is no choice I also do this an
hour I can't
get away from this and the
next I am shackled by this
desire I have no other choice what to
do in the next picture we didn't do
them don't look at the picture think
that I
know what it is in
[music]
you know that when you make a
channel and on channels and so on
you have channels
both Germans to blame there are channels
[music]
don't forget
Alex and should take the money most likely
Alicia is not money the law with that's why
go early and
account here we are talking about everyone and we
all have those necessary channels and
if you explain to me last maybe I will
allow you to go early tomorrow
so you can for breakfast we will
continue diamond  The path of
Vajra Vajrayana
to the request
since you have the ability
to achieve enlightenment, you were created
to do this, you have a chakra, you
have a great body, it was
created to achieve
enlightenment at the factory, it was already
conceived this way,
you since you have the gift, you are sitting
in the epicenter of tantric practices on this
planet,
not bad,
so I can achieve this, yes, what are you
waiting for,
we have a little time, I believe that
we should not waste a minute, we
have 5 minutes, so I will dive in a little,
next, do something, the edges will
not prepare
us about the world, even for you, not from pro,
perhaps there are some problems, and well, I will
just read to you, we
will look at the picture, tomorrow I will read to you what we
will study in the next lesson,
tell them,
Rome, this is a very famous movement,
these in Tibetan Buddhism, time means
systems,
non-joining schools, non-
united schools, and
schools that joined me, so
they became places, became schools,
not like Yarin, the belt went well
[music]
but here  This means it does
n't matter which school in the Tibetan school,
Leika, which school of ancient India you
belong to, it doesn't matter,
we are all lucky, we all
have these teachings to achieve
enlightenment,
but in general it is true that
regardless of
which school you follow, it will
lead to 20 enlightenment in one life,
tantric teachings in all schools can
lead you to enlightenment in one life,
and
in this
book, we are the same, and after that, he will
immediately say why, especially, this is true,
you cannot achieve enlightenment in you can
achieve enlightenment of the enemy, the
Tibetan tradition if you practice
the secret teachings in these practices, but he
says, but in the
subtle system, he says
you can achieve your goal in 12 years,
not very, very famous numbers, you can
achieve enlightenment and this and this comes
from tantra from ancient India,
you can reach your goal in 12 years, this is
not an opportunity, they have potions, you can
also speed up these things
[music]
three years,
not a system, the
subtle system when you can achieve
us three
enlightenment in three years, so he
says
you have a ripe one which was created  For
enlightenment, you are together, which
was built for these practices, and you
have the teachings and
any teachings that came to
help you achieve this in one lifetime, but
in an hour, and if you follow the teachings of
Zinc, you can achieve this in 12 years
or even in three years.
This has happened many times before.
You can simply read these
stories of religious people and understand what
happened to him. You can read the King of
Dharma. You can buy this book online
or get a bunch of easy ones. I really
like it. I have a science somewhere in the
region. I looked at it. Therefore, you
have
these reliable
stories of people and you can study them. The
King of Dharma is a good example. If you
carefully read this book, you
will understand why you achieved enlightenment in
one lifetime.
You are crazy if you don't read the book of
time because it is here, here is
what Karen Pogon is talking about. Why do you
see and read these systems for a year? You
will see what people will do. So, don't be lazy.
And
so, it's
his day, and
we'll see you tomorrow.